You had a question is that it has come out and
some new changes have happened in your portfolio,
see you have added some home finance companies
and removed your love partner's company
from your portfolio, it is creating a lot of value in the market, right now
I would like to explain against my graph of last 10-15 years,
first of all, we have got reservation,
about these changes, to
collect those points,
we have taken the company of Home Proposal, which was already available
in our portfolio, now it is also
in our Skin Capital portfolio
and Rai cigarette smoking was already there and on
top of that we have added a company named Home First of Home Finance,
if we click on the
subscribe button, the
series of affordable housing finance, that is, mortgage of 10
lakh valid rates like piston lights,
its stabilizer's home loan, which
shampoo looks quite attractive, here the
One India for employment is being created,
according to the data of this use,
in class 3 years, about 132 to 32 plain jobs have been
created, which is the series of employment
and the  The trend of formal employment that we are
seeing from the data of EPFO, its benefit from
this 10 lakh fifteen lakh of affordable housing finance from here is now in the air,
here housing and we are doing good work,
we are working on the proposal melodious voice,
universal education and both have been
killed, pollution is strong, their
asset quality management against branded
health, natural crisis, yes
bank, I will develop its specialty,
asset quality management has been strong,
waste technology is excellent, hence
from our channel going into rough going into
economic recovery, earnestly stress that
Corbett's post, he soiled the
recovery, it was a long way
forward, you have to type, you will get the website of Indian economic
recovery, good housing finance
from our channel, hence both
housing and eyes were
in our portfolio for many years,
last book, amazing company, more
definitely Balaji increased invisible for the last 15 years,
when I have done a lot in between till now,
and in distribution, especially
in Western India, there were some
challenges of distribution, class cooperative  Intensity
first in this piece apart from SP it has been made
crockery score live causal process has been added
then computer intensity is falling
and
looking good plaster last fifteen years
celebration in the space we thought that it would be
better to remove the stock then staff and add these finance companies so
you all felt Saurabh this is talking about changes
Gaurav wants to scrub your
modern and change your skin in
which your heart has been replaced
by consultant general James Jones on staff general
insurance exams rence such a person looks quite
attractive what night time
behind him Alembert
is the market leader in motor insurance out of 10 in private sector
and if motor insurance has
built such a knee franchise in the last 15 years we do
n't see any other player of this quality and
Misri Motor Insurance is one of those logically edge
industry here and will do about one *
half means half warrant 50% engine drivers
have motor insurance logically that is the biblical
situation record is a half-half country
festival and tell me inch and from this  So the
problem of insurance will increase. This is the most
profitable, best friend motor
insurance, and the
other reason for us to buy gallery or ad stuff is that
after VAT, corporate health cover
is individual. Discover that you are understanding
here. This is not the bond market leader. There are
no videos of Lakhan Sharma. If there are some
regulatory changes, the benefit will be seen in 2 years where it has become
easier for players like ICICI Lombard to enter the health insurance sector on a large scale. And the
attitude adopted by Chola in the management in the last six months
towards health insurance, we
feel that you
can make it a great performance in Islamabad but help. So,
in motor insurance, the market leader, help is expected to move towards
market leadership. It
is a good company. Well, ICICI Prudential has a
brand and the situation benefits it.